[High-pitched scream]
"I smile so they don't ask questions."
[Desperate scream]
"Some nights, even sleep feels like pain."
[Guttural scream in the distance]
"I'm surrounded, yet I've never felt more alone."
[Blood-curdling scream]
"Hope is a cruel joke I keep falling for."
[Shriek echoes and fades]
"Every laugh I fake costs a piece of me."
[Man screaming in anguish]
"I don’t know who I am anymore."
[Unnatural, distorted scream]
"They say time heals, but I only feel emptier."
[Choked scream, like someone sobbing]
"I wake up tired of waking up."
[Faint scream beneath static]
"The silence after the scream is worse."
[Sharp scream, quickly silenced]
"I'm a ghost in my own life."
[Series of frantic screams]
"No one notices you're falling apart if you fall quietly."
[Wailing in the background]
"My body moves, but my soul stayed behind."
[Scream with echo, then silence]
"I forgot how to feel anything but numb."
[Panicked scream fading]
"I don't want to die. I just don't want to exist like this."
[Crying, turning into a scream]
"The weight gets heavier every day."
[Multiple screams layered]
"If anyone heard my thoughts, they'd run."
[Scream suddenly cuts off]
"Some wounds aren't meant to heal."
[Silence... but it feels loud]